varunamultimedia.com 2014-11-11

# Varuna Multimedia Privacy Policy & Disclaimer

Our Privacy Policy for www.VarunaMultimedia.com and www.ThrimanaTV.com is given below. 

The privacy of our visitors to www.VarunaMultimedia.com and www.ThrimanaTV.com is important to us. At www.VarunaMultimedia.com and www.ThrimanaTV.com, we recognise that privacy of your personal information is important. Here is information on what types of personal information we receive and collect when you use and visit www.VarunaMultimedia.com and www.ThrimanaTV.com, and how we safeguard your information. 

**Log Files**

As with most other websites, we collect and use the data contained in log files. The information in the log files include your IP (internet protocol) address, your ISP (internet service provider, such as Big Pond, Optus or AOL), your geographical area (e.g. country and state), the browser you used to visit our site (such as Google Chrome, Internet Explorer or Firefox), the technology that you are using to access (PC, Mobile Phone, Tablet, etc.), the time you visited our site and which pages you visited throughout our site. However, we do NOT collect any other personal information about you. 

**Cookies and Web Beacons**

We do use cookies to store information, such as your personal preferences when you visit our site. We also use third party advertisements on www.VarunaMultimedia.com and www.ThrimanaTV.com to support our site. Some of these advertisers may use technology such as cookies and web beacons when they advertise on our site, which will also send these advertisers (such as Google Inc.) information including your IP address, your ISP, the browser you used to visit our site, and in some cases, whether you have Flash installed. This is generally used for geotargeting purposes (showing Sydney real estate ads to someone in Sydney, for example) or showing certain ads based on specific sites visited (such as showing cooking ads to someone who frequents cooking sites).

**DoubleClick DART cookies**

We also may use DART cookies for ad serving through Google’s DoubleClick, which places a cookie on your computer or device when you are browsing the web and visit a site using DoubleClick advertising (including some Google AdSense advertisements). This cookie is used to serve ads specific to you and your interests (”interest based targeting”).

The ads served will be targeted based on your previous browsing history (For example, if you have been viewing sites about visiting Melbourne, you may see Melbourne hotel advertisements when viewing a non-related site, such as on a site about Cricket). DART uses “non personally identifiable information”. It does NOT track personal information about you.

You can opt-out of this ad serving on all sites using this advertising by visiting http://www.aboutads.info/ or http://www.doubleclick.com/privacy/dart_adserving.aspx 

You can choose to disable or selectively turn off our cookies or third-party cookies in your browser settings, or by managing preferences in Internet-Security programs. However, this can affect how you are able to interact with our site as well as other websites. This could include the inability to login to services or programs, such as logging into forums.

Deleting cookies does not mean you are permanently opted out of any advertising program. Unless you have settings that disallow cookies, the next time you visit a site running the advertisements, a new cookie will be added.

Varuna Multimedia Productions may revise this Privacy Policy at any time by updating this posting. This privacy statement was last modified on the 06th of October 2013. 

This disclaimer applies to the information and data given on this Site. 

Varuna Multimedia has attempted to make the information on this Site as accurate as possible and is provided in good faith without any express or implied warranty. There is no guarantee given as to the accuracy of any individual item on the Site. If you rely on the information given on this Site, you are responsible for ensuring by independent verification its accuracy, currency or completeness. The information given on this Site is for personal use only. 

Varuna Multimedia Productions, its agents, instrumentalities and associates make no warranties, representations, express or implied, as to the accuracy, merchantability, quality or fitness for purpose of the information and data contained on this Site. You accept all risks and responsibility for losses, damages, costs and other consequences resulting directly or indirectly from using this site and any information or material available from it. To the maximum permitted by law, Varuna Multimedia Productions, its agents, instrumentalities and associates excludes all liability to any person arising directly or indirectly from using this site and any information or material available from it. 

This Site includes links to other websites. Other websites include links to this Site. All linked websites are linked "as is" and Varuna Multimedia Productions, its agents, instrumentalities and associates do not necessarily endorse or approve of any material on websites linked from or to this Site; does not make any warranties or representations regarding the quality, accuracy, merchantability or fitness for purpose of any material on websites linked from or to this Site. 

The automated video discovery system of this site automatically creates and manages links to the publicly available video content interested to the visitors of this site. This site includes automatically created and managed links to Youtube™ hosted video clips. If you are the copyright owner of any of those videos and you wish to remove a video, inform Youtube™ to remove the video from Youtube™ servers on Copyright grounds. This [ form ](http://www.youtube.com/yt/copyright/copyright-complaint.html) may be used to lodge a Copyright Infrigement Notification requesting to remove a video on Copyright grounds (http://www.youtube.com/yt/copyright/copyright-complaint.html). Once a video is removed from Youtube™, it will automatically be removed from this site. Alternatvely, you may consider monetising your copyrighted video content hosted by Youtube™. More details can be found [ here ](https://support.google.com/youtube/answer/2797370?hl=en)(https://support.google.com/youtube/answer/2797370?hl=en).

The information on this Site is subject to change without notice. Varuna Multimedia Productions may revise this Disclaimer at any time by updating this posting. This statement was last modified on the 11th January 2014.
